<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
    <info>
        <name>The Warlock Remastered</name>
        <update version="0.0.1">
            <file name="warlock-remastered-invocation.xml"/>
        </update>
    </info>

    <!-- Eldritch Invocations -->
    <element name="All Else Equal" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ALL_ELSE_EQUAL">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>
                <em>Prerequisite: 7th level, Pact of the Blade</em>
            </p>
            <p>Whenever you cast a spell with the word “smite” in the name, you can choose to have it function with
                cantrips that require an attack roll, and any weapon attack, rather than only melee weapon attacks. A
                cantrip benefiting from a “smite” spell deals damage as if a 1st-level character had cast it.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Whenever you cast a spell with the word “smite” in the name, you can choose to have it function
                with cantrips that require an attack roll, and any weapon attack, rather than only melee weapon attacks.
                A cantrip benefiting from a “smite” spell deals damage as if a 1st-level character had cast it.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Armor of Shadows" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ARMOR_OF_SHADOWS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>mage armor</em> on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material
                components.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast mage armor on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material
                components.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Ascendant Step" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ASCENDANT_STEP">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>9th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:9]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>
                <em>Prerequisite: 9th level</em>
            </p>
            <p>You can cast <em>levitate</em> on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material
                components.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast levitate on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material
                components.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Aspect of the Moon" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ASPECT_OF_THE_MOON">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Tome</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_TOME</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You no longer need to sleep and can't be forced to sleep by any means. To gain the benefits of a long
                rest, you can spend all 8 hours doing light activity, such as reading your Book of Shadows and keeping
                watch.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You no longer need to sleep and can't be forced to sleep by any means. To gain the benefits of
                a long rest, you can spend all 8 hours doing light activity, such as reading your Book of Shadows and
                keeping watch.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Awakened Weapon" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_AWAKENED_WEAPON">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Archfey patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_WOTC_PHB_ARCHETYPE_OTHERWORLDLY_PATRON_THE_ARCHFEY</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can choose to create a weapon from polished black wood and wicked spines using your Pact of the Blade
                feature. While you maintain concentration on a spell cast using a warlock spell slot while wielding this
                weapon, dense foliage covers your skin, causing your AC to equal 17 if it would normally be lower.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can choose to create a weapon from polished black wood and wicked spines using your Pact of
                the Blade feature. While you maintain concentration on a spell cast using a warlock spell slot while
                wielding this weapon, dense foliage covers your skin, causing your AC to equal 17 if it would normally
                be lower.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Beast Speech" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_BEAST_SPEECH">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>speak with animals</em> at will, without expending a spell slot.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast speak with animals at will, without expending a spell slot.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Beguiling Influence" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_BEGUILING_INFLUENCE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You gain proficiency in the Deception and Persuasion skills. If you are already proficient with either or
                both of those skills, your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make that uses that
                proficiency.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You gain proficiency in the Deception and Persuasion skills. If you are already proficient with
                either or both of those skills, your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make that
                uses that proficiency.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Bewitching Whispers" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_BEWITCHING_WHISPERS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>compulsion</em> once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you
                finish a long rest.
            </p>
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_COMPULSION"/>
            </div>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast compulsion once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until
                you finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_COMPULSION"/>
        </rules>
    </element>

    <element name="Blade Empowerment" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_BLADE_EMPOWERMENT">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>As a bonus action, you can empower your pact weapon with eldritch energy. The first time you hit a
                creature with an empowered pact weapon before the start of your next turn, it takes additional force
                damage equal to half your warlock level and if the attack was a critical hit, the target is knocked
                prone.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>As a bonus action, you can empower your pact weapon with eldritch energy. The first time you
                hit a creature with an empowered pact weapon before the start of your next turn, it takes additional
                force damage equal to half your warlock level and if the attack was a critical hit, the target is
                knocked prone.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Bond of the Chain Master" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_BOND_OF_THE_CHAIN_MASTER">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Chain feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_CHAIN</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>Whenever you cast a warlock spell that targets you or has a range of self, you can have the spell also
                target your familiar if it is within 100 feet of you. Additionally, you can cast warding bond once on
                your familiar without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability to do so when you finish a long
                rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Whenever you cast a warlock spell that targets you or has a range of self, you can have the
                spell also target your familiar if it is within 100 feet of you. Additionally, you can cast warding bond
                once on your familiar without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability to do so when you finish a
                long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Captured Heart" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_CAPTURED_HEART">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>

        <description>
            <p>You gain advantage on attack rolls targeting creatures that you have charmed. If you attack a creature
                you have charmed, it can’t take reactions until the end of your next turn.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You gain advantage on attack rolls targeting creatures that you have charmed. If you attack a
                creature you have charmed, it can’t take reactions until the end of your next turn.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Chains of Carceri" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_CHAINS_OF_CARCERI">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>15th level, Pact of the Chain</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_CHAIN</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>hold monster</em> at will—targeting a celestial, fiend, or elemental — without expending
                a spell slot or material components. You must finish a long rest before you can use this invocation on
                the same creature again.
            </p>
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_HOLD_MONSTER"/>
            </div>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast hold monster at will—targeting a celestial, fiend, or elemental — without
                expending a spell slot or material components. You must finish a long rest before you can use this
                invocation on the same creature again.
            </description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HOLD_MONSTER"/>
        </rules>
    </element>
    <element name="Improved Pact Weapon" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_IMPROVED_PACT_WEAPON">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>

        <description>
            <p>Any weapon you summon with your Pact of the Blade feature gains a +1 bonus to its attack and damage
                rolls, unless it is a magic weapon that already has a bonus to those rolls. At 9th level, this bonus
                increases to +2, and at 15th level, +3.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Any weapon you summon with your Pact of the Blade feature gains a +1 bonus to its attack and
                damage rolls, unless it is a magic weapon that already has a bonus to those rolls. At 9th level, this
                bonus increases to +2, and at 15th level, +3.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Cloak of Flies" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_CLOAK_OF_FLIES">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>As a bonus action, you can surround yourself with a magical aura that looks like buzzing flies. The aura
                extends 5 feet from you in every direction, but not through total cover. It lasts until you're
                incapacitated or you dismiss it as a bonus action. The aura grants you advantage on Charisma
                (Intimidation) checks but disadvantage on all other Charisma checks. Any other creature that starts its
                turn in the aura takes poison damage equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1
                damage).
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>As a bonus action, you can surround yourself with a magical aura that looks like buzzing flies.
                The aura extends 5 feet from you in every direction, but not through total cover. It lasts until you're
                incapacitated or you dismiss it as a bonus action. The aura grants you advantage on Charisma
                (Intimidation) checks but disadvantage on all other Charisma checks. Any other creature that starts its
                turn in the aura takes poison damage equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1
                damage).
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Curse Bringer" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_CURSE_BRINGER">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Dreadlord patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_OTHERWORDLY_PATRON_DREADLORD</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can create a weapon forged from silver, with umbral runes etched into it, using your Pact of the
                Blade feature. When a creature affected by your Curse of Gloom would hit you with an attack, you can use
                your reaction to increase your AC against the attack by an amount equal to your warlock spellcasting
                ability modifier. If the attack still hits, the attacker takes extra damage equal to half your warlock
                level. The extra damage is the weapon's damage type.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can create a weapon forged from silver, with umbral runes etched into it, using your Pact
                of the Blade feature. When a creature affected by your Curse of Gloom would hit you with an attack, you
                can use your reaction to increase your AC against the attack by an amount equal to your warlock
                spellcasting ability modifier. If the attack still hits, the attacker takes extra damage equal to half
                your warlock level. The extra damage is the weapon's damage type.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Devil's Sight" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_DEVILS_SIGHT">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can see normally in darkness, both magical and nonmagical, to a distance of 120 feet.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can see normally in darkness, both magical and nonmagical, to a distance of 120 feet.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Dreadful Word" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_DREADFUL_WORD">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>confusion</em> once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you
                finish a long rest.
            </p>
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONFUSION"/>
            </div>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast confusion once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you
                finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONFUSION"/>
        </rules>
    </element>
    <element name="Eldritch Armor" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ELDRITCH_ARMOR">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can transform one magical or mundane armor into your pact armor by performing a special ritual while
                touching the armor. You're always proficient in your pact armor. When using an action to summon it, you
                can also choose to summon your pact weapon with the same action. You may use your warlock spellcasting
                ability score instead of your Strength score for purposes of speed reduction and the usage of heavy
                armor.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can transform one magical or mundane armor into your pact armor by performing a special
                ritual while touching the armor. You're always proficient in your pact armor. When using an action to
                summon it, you can also choose to summon your pact weapon with the same action. You may use your warlock
                spellcasting ability score instead of your Strength score for purposes of speed reduction and the usage
                of heavy armor.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Eldritch Mind" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ELDRITCH_MIND">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Tome feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_TOME</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You have advantage on Constitution saving throws that you make to maintain your concentration on a
                spell.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You have advantage on Constitution saving throws that you make to maintain your concentration
                on a spell.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Eldritch Sight" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ELDRITCH_SIGHT">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>detect magic</em> at will, without expending a spell slot.
            </p>
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_DETECT_MAGIC"/>
            </div>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast detect magic at will, without expending a spell slot.</description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DETECT_MAGIC"/>
        </rules>
    </element>
    <element name="Eldritch Spear" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ELDRITCH_SPEAR">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>When you cast a warlock cantrip that requires a ranged spell attack, its range is increased to 300
                feet.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>When you cast a warlock cantrip that requires a ranged spell attack, its range is increased to
                300 feet.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Eyes of the Rune Keeper" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_EYES_OF_THE_RUNE_KEEPER">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can read all writing.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can read all writing.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Far Scribe" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_FAR_SCRIBE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level, Pact of the Tome feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_TOME</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>A new page appears in your Book of Erudition. With your permission, a creature can use its action to
                write its name on that page, which can contain a number of names equal to your warlock spellcasting
                ability modifier (minimum of 1). You can cast the sending spell, targeting a creature whose name is on
                the page, without using a spell slot and without using material components. To do so, you must write the
                message on the page. The target hears the message in their mind, and if the target replies, their
                message appears on the page, rather than in your mind. The writing disappears after 1 minute. As an
                action, you can magically erase a name on the page by touching the name on it.
            </p>
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_SENDING"/>
            </div>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>A new page appears in your Book of Erudition. With your permission, a creature can use its
                action to write its name on that page, which can contain a number of names equal to your warlock
                spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1). You can cast the sending spell, targeting a creature whose
                name is on the page, without using a spell slot and without using material components. To do so, you
                must write the message on the page. The target hears the message in their mind, and if the target
                replies, their message appears on the page, rather than in your mind. The writing disappears after 1
                minute. As an action, you can magically erase a name on the page by touching the name on it.
            </description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SENDING"/>
        </rules>
    </element>

    <element name="Vigor of the Lost" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_VIGOR_OF_THE_LOST">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast <em>false life</em> on yourself at will as a 1st-level spell, without expending a spell slot
                or material components. Additionally, when you fail a death saving throw, you can instead choose to
                succeed. If you do, you lose the benefits of this invocation until you finish a long rest.
            </p>
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_FALSE_LIFE"/>
            </div>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast false life on yourself at will as a 1st-level spell, without expending a spell
                slot or material components. Additionally, when you fail a death saving throw, you can instead choose to
                succeed. If you do, you lose the benefits of this invocation until you finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FALSE_LIFE"/>
        </rules>
    </element>

    <element name="Gaze of Two Minds" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GAZE_OF_TWO_MINDS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can use your action to touch a willing humanoid and perceive through its senses until the end of your
                next turn. As long as the creature is on the same plane of existence as you, you can use your action on
                subsequent turns to maintain this connection, extending the duration until the end of your next turn.
                While perceiving through the other creature's senses, you benefit from any special senses possessed by
                that creature, and you are blinded and deafened to your own surroundings.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can use your action to touch a willing humanoid and perceive through its senses until the
                end of your next turn. As long as the creature is on the same plane of existence as you, you can use
                your action on subsequent turns to maintain this connection, extending the duration until the end of
                your next turn. While perceiving through the other creature's senses, you benefit from any special
                senses possessed by that creature, and you are blinded and deafened to your own surroundings.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Flaywind Blade" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_FLAYWIND_BLADE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Radiant Storm Patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_OTHERWORDLY_PATRON_RADIANT_STORM,
            ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE
        </requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you create a weapon with your Pact of the Blade feature, you can infuse it with silver mist and form
                it from stormscarred steel. You can choose to have this weapon deal lightning or thunder damage. When a
                ranged attack misses you while you are wielding this weapon, you can use your reaction to move up to 15
                feet without provoking opportunity attacks, and you can move through spaces occupied by hostile
                creatures without spending additional movement.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>When you create a weapon with your Pact of the Blade feature, you can infuse it with silver
                mist and form it from stormscarred steel. You can choose to have this weapon deal lightning or thunder
                damage. When a ranged attack misses you while you are wielding this weapon, you can use your reaction to
                move up to 15 feet without provoking opportunity attacks, and you can move through spaces occupied by
                hostile creatures without spending additional movement.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Ghostly Gaze" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GHOSTLY_GAZE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>As an action, you gain the ability to see through solid objects to a range of 30 feet. Within that range,
                you have darkvision if you don't already have it. This special sight lasts for 1 minute or until your
                concentration ends (as if you were concentrating on a spell). During that time, you perceive objects as
                ghostly, transparent images.
            </p>
            <p>Once you use this invocation, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>As an action, you gain the ability to see through solid objects to a range of 30 feet. Within
                that range, you have darkvision if you don't already have it. This special sight lasts for 1 minute or
                until your concentration ends (as if you were concentrating on a spell). During that time, you perceive
                objects as ghostly, transparent images.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Gift of the Depths" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GIFT_OF_THE_DEPTHS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can breathe underwater, and you gain a swimming speed equal to your walking speed.</p>
            <p>You can also cast <em>water breathing</em> once without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability to
                do so when you finish a long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can breathe underwater, and you gain a swimming speed equal to your walking speed. You can
                also cast water breathing once without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability to do so when you
                finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Gift of the Ever-Living Ones" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GIFT_OF_THE_EVER_LIVING_ONES">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Chain</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_CHAIN</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>Whenever you regain hit points while your familiar is within 100 feet of you, treat any dice rolled to
                determine the hit points you regain as having rolled their maximum value for you.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Whenever you regain hit points while your familiar is within 100 feet of you, treat any dice
                rolled to determine the hit points you regain as having rolled their maximum value for you.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Gift of the Protectors" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GIFT_OF_THE_PROTECTORS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>9th level, Pact of the Tome feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:9],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_TOME</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>A new page appears in your Book of Erudition. With your permission, a creature can use its action to
                write its name on that page, which can contain a number of names equal to your warlock spellcasting
                ability modifier (minimum of 1). When any creature whose name is on the page is reduced to 0 hit points
                but not killed outright, the creature magically drops to 1 hit point instead. Once this magic is
                triggered, no creature can benefit from it until you finish a long rest. As an action, you can magically
                erase a name on the page by touching the name on it.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>A new page appears in your Book of Erudition. With your permission, a creature can use its
                action to write its name on that page, which can contain a number of names equal to your warlock
                spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1). When any creature whose name is on the page is reduced to
                0 hit points but not killed outright, the creature magically drops to 1 hit point instead. Once this
                magic is triggered, no creature can benefit from it until you finish a long rest. As an action, you can
                magically erase a name on the page by touching the name on it.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Grasp of Hadar" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GRASP_OF_HADAR">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a warlock cantrip that requires a ranged spell
                attack, you can move that creature in a straight line 10 feet closer to you.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a warlock cantrip that requires a
                ranged spell attack, you can move that creature in a straight line 10 feet closer to you.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Otherworldly Training" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_OTHERWORLDLY_TRAINING">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You gain one fighting style from the Fighter class. At the end of a long rest, you can change the
                fighting style you know with another available fighting style.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You gain one fighting style from the Fighter class. At the end of a long rest, you can change
                the fighting style you know with another available fighting style.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Touch of the Ancient One" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_TOUCH_OF_THE_ANCIENT_ONE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Great Old One, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>
            ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PATRON_OTHERWORLDLY_PATRON_THE_GREAT_OLD_ONE,ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE
        </requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you create a weapon using your Pact of the Blade feature, you can make it from aberrant flesh,
                twitching with eyes and mouths. You can choose to deal psychic damage with this weapon. Once per turn,
                you can cause your attacks to become mentally toxic. If you do so, the creature has disadvantage on the
                next attack roll it makes before the end of its next turn. During the first round of combat, attacks
                with this weapon deal extra psychic damage equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier plus half
                your warlock level.
            </p>
            <p>Additionally, when you hit a creature with a weapon attack made with your pact weapon, you can glimpse
                into its mind. You immediately learn if the creature is under any mind-influencing effects and what
                those effects are, such as a geas spell, and learn the creature's greatest fears and desires. Once you
                glimpse a creature's mind, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>When you create a weapon using your Pact of the Blade feature, you can make it from aberrant
                flesh, twitching with eyes and mouths. You can choose to deal psychic damage with this weapon. Once per
                turn, you can cause your attacks to become mentally toxic. If you do so, the creature has disadvantage
                on the next attack roll it makes before the end of its next turn. During the first round of combat,
                attacks with this weapon deal extra psychic damage equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier
                plus half your warlock level.
            </description>
            <description>Additionally, when you hit a creature with a weapon attack made with your pact weapon, you can
                glimpse into its mind. You immediately learn if the creature is under any mind-influencing effects and
                what those effects are, such as a geas spell, and learn the creature's greatest fears and desires. Once
                you glimpse a creature's mind, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Hide of Cinders" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_HIDE_OF_CINDERS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Fiend patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>
            ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PATRON_OTHERWORLDLY_PATRON_THE_FIEND,ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE
        </requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can summon a coating of embers and ash to cover your skin, protecting you from harm. You can choose
                to have your AC equal 10 + your Dexterity modifier + your warlock spellcasting ability modifier. If a
                creature hits you with a melee attack while this armor is active, you can use your reaction to deal fire
                damage to the creature equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can summon a coating of embers and ash to cover your skin, protecting you from harm. You
                can choose to have your AC equal 10 + your Dexterity modifier + your warlock spellcasting ability
                modifier. If a creature hits you with a melee attack while this armor is active, you can use your
                reaction to deal fire damage to the creature equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Lance of Lethargy" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_LANCE_OF_LETHARGY">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a warlock cantrip that requires a ranged spell
                attack, you can reduce that creature's speed by 10 feet until the end of your next turn.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a warlock cantrip that requires a
                ranged spell attack, you can reduce that creature's speed by 10 feet until the end of your next turn.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Lifedrinker" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_LIFEDRINKER">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>12th level, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:12],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you hit a creature with your pact weapon, the creature takes extra force damage equal to your
                warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1).
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>When you hit a creature with your pact weapon, the creature takes extra force damage equal to
                your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1).
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Limitless Weapon" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_LIMITLESS_WEAPON">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>While you have this invocation, you gain the ability to modify your pact weapon with greater ease. If
                your pact weapon is an attuned magic weapon, rather than one you have created, you can shift its form to
                any weapon you could normally create using your Pact of the Blade feature when you summon it.
                Additionally, you can apply the benefits of any invocation that requires you to create your pact weapon,
                such as Scorched Blade, as long as it is in the appropriate form to meet that invocation’s requirements.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>While you have this invocation, you gain the ability to modify your pact weapon with greater
                ease. If your pact weapon is an attuned magic weapon, rather than one you have created, you can shift
                its form to any weapon you could normally create using your Pact of the Blade feature when you summon
                it. Additionally, you can apply the benefits of any invocation that requires you to create your pact
                weapon, such as Scorched Blade, as long as it is in the appropriate form to meet that invocation’s
                requirements.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Maddening Hex" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MADDENING_HEX">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level, hex spell or a warlock feature that curses</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5],ID_PHB_SPELL_HEX</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>As a bonus action, you cause a psychic disturbance around the target cursed by your hex spell or by a
                warlock feature of yours, such as Curse of Gloom or Sign of Ill Omen. When you do so, you deal psychic
                damage to the cursed target and each creature of your choice that you can see within 5 feet of it. The
                psychic damage equals your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1 damage). To use this
                invocation, you must be able to see the cursed target, and it must be within 30 feet of you.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>As a bonus action, you cause a psychic disturbance around the target cursed by your hex spell
                or by a warlock feature of yours, such as Curse of Gloom or Sign of Ill Omen. When you do so, you deal
                psychic damage to the cursed target and each creature of your choice that you can see within 5 feet of
                it. The psychic damage equals your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of 1 damage). To use
                this invocation, you must be able to see the cursed target, and it must be within 30 feet of you.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Mask of Many Faces" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MASK_OF_MANY_FACES">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast disguise self at will, without expending a spell slot.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast disguise self at will, without expending a spell slot.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Master of Myriad Forms" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MASTER_OF_MYRIAD_FORMS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>15th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:15]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast alter self at will, without expending a spell slot.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast alter self at will, without expending a spell slot.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Minions of Chaos" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MINIONS_OF_CHAOS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>9th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:9]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast conjure elemental once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you
                finish a long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast conjure elemental once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again
                until you finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Mire the Mind" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MIRE_THE_MIND">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast slow once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long
                rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast slow once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you
                finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Misty Visions" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MISTY_VISIONS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast silent image at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast silent image at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="One with Shadows" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ONE_WITH_SHADOWS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you are in an area of dim light or darkness, you can use your action to become invisible until you
                move or take an action or a reaction.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>When you are in an area of dim light or darkness, you can use your action to become invisible
                until you move or take an action or a reaction.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Otherworldly Leap" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_OTHERWORLDLY_LEAP">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast jump on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast jump on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Relentless Hex" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_RELENTLESS_HEX">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level, hex spell or a warlock feature that curses</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7],ID_PHB_SPELL_HEX</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>Your curse creates a temporary bond between you and your target. As a bonus action, you can magically
                teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space you can see within 5 feet of the target cursed by your hex
                spell or by a warlock feature of yours, such as Dreadlord Curse or Sign of Ill Omen. To teleport in this
                way, you must be able to see the cursed target.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Your curse creates a temporary bond between you and your target. As a bonus action, you can
                magically teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space you can see within 5 feet of the target cursed
                by your hex spell or by a warlock feature of yours, such as Dreadlord Curse or Sign of Ill Omen. To
                teleport in this way, you must be able to see the cursed target.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Repelling Blast" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_REPELLING_BLAST">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>When you hit a creature with a warlock cantrip that requires a ranged spell attack, you can push the
                creature up to 10 feet away from you in a straight line.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>When you hit a creature with a warlock cantrip that requires a ranged spell attack, you can
                push the creature up to 10 feet away from you in a straight line.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Revealer of Secrets" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_REVEALER_OF_SECRETS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast identify at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast identify at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Scorched Weapon" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_SCORCHED_WEAPON">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Fiend patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_OTHERWORDLY_PATRON_FIEND,ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE
        </requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can create a wickedly barbed weapon made from embers and molten steel using your Pact of the Blade
                feature. You can choose to have this weapon deal fire damage. Whenever a creature within your reach
                takes damage directly due to hitting you with an attack, such as from the effect of the fire shield
                spell, you can use your reaction to make an opportunity attack against your attacker using this weapon.
                If the spell or feature that would deal damage to the attacker requires a reaction, such as the Hide of
                Cinders invocation, you can make the opportunity attack as part of the same reaction. Once you do so,
                you can’t do so again until you finish a short or long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can create a wickedly barbed weapon made from embers and molten steel using your Pact of
                the Blade feature. You can choose to have this weapon deal fire damage. Whenever a creature within your
                reach takes damage directly due to hitting you with an attack, such as from the effect of the fire
                shield spell, you can use your reaction to make an opportunity attack against your attacker using this
                weapon. If the spell or feature that would deal damage to the attacker requires a reaction, such as the
                Hide of Cinders invocation, you can make the opportunity attack as part of the same reaction. Once you
                do so, you can’t do so again until you finish a short or long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Sculptor of Flesh" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_SCULPTOR_OF_FLESH">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast polymorph once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a
                long rest. When you cast polymorph this way, you can allow the creature to retain its mental ability
                scores. Additionally, you can use your action to change the form of the affected creature. If the new
                form has more hit points than the current one, the creature's hit points remain at their current value.
                Otherwise, you assume the beast's hit points as normal.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast polymorph once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you
                finish a long rest. When you cast polymorph this way, you can allow the creature to retain its mental
                ability scores. Additionally, you can use your action to change the form of the affected creature. If
                the new form has more hit points than the current one, the creature's hit points remain at their current
                value. Otherwise, you assume the beast's hit points as normal.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <element name="Shroud of Shadow" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_SHROUD_OF_SHADOW">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>15th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:15]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast invisibility at will, without expending a spell slot.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can cast invisibility at will, without expending a spell slot.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Sign of Ill Omen -->
    <element name="Sign of Ill Omen" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_SIGN_OF_ILL_OMEN">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast bestow curse once without using a spell slot, as if it was cast using one of your Pact Magic
                spell slots. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest. When you obtain your Mystic Arcanum
                feature, you can use it to cast bestow curse.
            </p>
            <p>When you cast the spell this way, you can force the target to make a Charisma saving throw instead of a
                Wisdom saving throw. Additionally, you can sense the target's location and see them clearly for the
                duration of the spell, even through full cover and magical obscuration.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast bestow curse once without using a spell slot, as if it was cast using one of your Pact
                Magic spell slots. When you cast the spell this way, you can force the target to make a Charisma saving
                throw instead of a Wisdom saving throw. Additionally, you can sense the target's location and see them
                clearly for the duration of the spell, even through full cover and magical obscuration.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Sorrowfield -->
    <element name="Sorrowfield" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_SORROWFIELD">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Dreadlord Patron, 9th Level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_OTHERWORDLY_PATRON_DREADLORD,[level:9]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you activate your Curse of Gloom, you may expend a warlock spell slot and target a number of
                creatures equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of one) you can see within 30
                feet. Each creature is now affected by your Curse of Gloom. When you use this ability, you only regain
                hit points from the first cursed creature that dies.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                When you activate your Curse of Gloom, you may expend a warlock spell slot and target a number of
                creatures equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum of one) you can see within 30
                feet. Each creature is now affected by your Curse of Gloom. When you use this ability, you only regain
                hit points from the first cursed creature that dies.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- The Silver Tongue -->
    <element name="The Silver Tongue" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_THE_SILVER_TONGUE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Archfey patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>
            ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_OTHERWORDLY_PATRON_ARCHFEY,ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_THE_BLADE
        </requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can create a weapon made of silver and bone using your Pact of the Blade feature. This weapon deals
                psychic damage instead of its normal damage type. When you hit a creature with this weapon, you can
                choose to deal no damage. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw against your warlock spell save DC.
                If they fail, they are charmed or frightened by you until the start of your next turn and will not take
                hostile actions against you, but may target your companions.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can create a weapon made of silver and bone using your Pact of the Blade feature. This weapon deals
                psychic damage instead of its normal damage type. When you hit a creature with this weapon, you can
                choose to deal no damage. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw against your warlock spell save DC.
                If they fail, they are charmed or frightened by you until the start of your next turn and will not take
                hostile actions against you, but may target your companions.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Thief of Five Fates -->
    <element name="Thief of Five Fates" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_THIEF_OF_FIVE_FATES">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>9th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:9]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast bane once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long
                rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast bane once without using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long
                rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Tomb of Levistus -->
    <element name="Tomb of Levistus" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_TOMB_OF_LEVISTUS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>As a reaction when you take damage, you can entomb yourself in ice, which melts away at the end of your
                next turn. You gain 10 temporary hit points per warlock level, which take as much of the triggering
                damage as possible. Immediately after you take the damage, you gain vulnerability to fire damage, your
                speed is reduced to 0, and you are incapacitated. These effects, including any remaining temporary hit
                points, all end when the ice melts.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                As a reaction when you take damage, you can entomb yourself in ice, which melts away at the end of your
                next turn. You gain 10 temporary hit points per warlock level, which take as much of the triggering
                damage as possible. Immediately after you take the damage, you gain vulnerability to fire damage, your
                speed is reduced to 0, and you are incapacitated. These effects, including any remaining temporary hit
                points, all end when the ice melts.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Trickster's Escape -->
    <element name="Trickster's Escape" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_TRICKSTERS_ESCAPE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast freedom of movement once on yourself without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability
                to do so when you finish a long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast freedom of movement once on yourself without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability
                to do so when you finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Thirsting Steel -->
    <element name="Thirsting Steel" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_THIRSTING_STEEL">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level, Pact of the Blade feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5], [pact:blade]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>If you miss with an attack roll using your pact weapon on your turn, you can make an additional attack
                with it. You can use this feature only once on each of your turns.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                If you miss with an attack roll using your pact weapon on your turn, you can make an additional attack
                with it. You can use this feature only once on each of your turns.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Twinned Blades -->
    <element name="Twinned Blades" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_TWINNED_BLADES">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[pact:blade]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You gain access to a second pact weapon, and you can summon both whenever you would summon one of them.
                When you engage in two-weapon fighting using both your pact weapons, you can add your ability modifier
                to the damage of the bonus attack.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You gain access to a second pact weapon, and you can summon both whenever you would summon one of them.
                When you engage in two-weapon fighting using both your pact weapons, you can add your ability modifier
                to the damage of the bonus attack.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Visions of Distant Realms -->
    <element name="Visions of Distant Realms" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_VISIONS_OF_DISTANT_REALMS">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>15th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:15]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast arcane eye at will, without expending a spell slot.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast arcane eye at will, without expending a spell slot.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Weapon of Dawn -->
    <element name="Weapon of Dawn" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_WEAPON_OF_DAWN">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Celestial patron, Pact of the Blade feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[patron:celestial], [pact:blade]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can create a weapon from worked stone infused with golden metal using your Pact of the Blade feature.
                At creation, you can choose to have this weapon deal radiant damage. A target hit by this weapon cannot
                make opportunity attacks targeting creatures other than you until the start of your next turn.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can create a weapon from worked stone infused with golden metal using your Pact of the Blade
                feature. At creation, you can choose to have this weapon deal radiant damage. A target hit by this
                weapon cannot make opportunity attacks targeting creatures other than you until the start of your next
                turn.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Weapon of the Lifetaker -->
    <element name="Weapon of the Lifetaker" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_WEAPON_OF_THE_LIFETAKER">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Undying patron, Pact of the Blade feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[patron:undying], [pact:blade]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can create a weapon of polished bone and golden metal using your Pact of the Blade feature. This
                weapon deals necrotic damage instead of its normal damage type. On a hit, you can cast inflict pain as a
                bonus action using a warlock spell slot.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can create a weapon of polished bone and golden metal using your Pact of the Blade feature. This
                weapon deals necrotic damage instead of its normal damage type. On a hit, you can cast inflict pain as a
                bonus action using a warlock spell slot.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Whispers of the Grave -->
    <element name="Whispers of the Grave" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_WHISPERS_OF_THE_GRAVE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>9th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:9]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast speak with dead at will, without expending a spell slot.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast speak with dead at will, without expending a spell slot.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Witch Sight -->
    <element name="Witch Sight" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_WITCH_SIGHT">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>15th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:15]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can see the true form of any shapechanger or creature concealed by illusion or transmutation magic
                while the creature is within 30 feet of you and within line of sight.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can see the true form of any shapechanger or creature concealed by illusion or transmutation magic
                while the creature is within 30 feet of you and within line of sight.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Alter Overflow: Backblast -->
    <element name="Alter Overflow: Backblast" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ALTER_OVERFLOW_BACKBLAST">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you hit a creature with an attack or cantrip and use your Eldritch Overflow feature, you can cause a
                backblast of arcane power. Every creature in a 15-foot cone directly behind the creature you hit must
                make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they are treated as having been successfully affected by
                the attack or cantrip, and take additional damage equal to your Eldritch Overflow damage die.
            </p>
            <p>You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns. Once you use this invocation, you must
                finish a short or long rest before you can do it again.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                When you hit a creature with an attack or cantrip and use your Eldritch Overflow feature, you can cause
                a backblast of arcane power. Every creature in a 15-foot cone directly behind the creature you hit must
                make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they are treated as having been successfully affected by
                the attack or cantrip, and take additional damage equal to your Eldritch Overflow damage die.
                You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns. Once you use this invocation, you must
                finish a short or long rest before you can do it again.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Alter Overflow: Eldritch Beam -->
    <element name="Alter Overflow: Eldritch Beam" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ALTER_OVERFLOW_ELDRITCH_BEAM">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you cast a damaging cantrip, you can release the spell's energy as a 5-foot wide, 100-foot long beam
                of arcane power originating from you. Each creature in the area must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a
                failure, they are treated as having been successfully affected by the cantrip, and take additional
                damage equal to your Eldritch Overflow damage die.
            </p>
            <p>You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns. Once you use this invocation, you must
                finish a short or long rest before you can do it again.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                When you cast a damaging cantrip, you can release the spell's energy as a 5-foot wide, 100-foot long
                beam of arcane power originating from you. Each creature in the area must make a Dexterity saving throw.
                On a failure, they are treated as having been successfully affected by the cantrip, and take additional
                damage equal to your Eldritch Overflow damage die.
                You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns. Once you use this invocation, you must
                finish a short or long rest before you can do it again.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Revival of the Unhallowed -->
    <element name="Revival of the Unhallowed" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_REVIVAL_OF_THE_UNHALLOWED">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast animate dead once using a warlock spell slot. When you cast this spell, you can animate dead
                and reassert control over existing undead at the same time. You can't cast this spell this way again
                until you finish a long rest.
            </p>
            <p>Additionally, when you cast animate dead you can forgo animating three undead to instead animate the
                remains of one Large humanoid or giant. The resulting undead uses the statistics of a Minotaur Zombie if
                you target bones, or an Ogre Zombie if you target a corpse. You treat this creature as three corpses for
                the purpose of reasserting control over it.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast animate dead once using a warlock spell slot. When you cast this spell, you can animate
                dead and reassert control over existing undead at the same time. You can't cast this spell this way
                again until you finish a long rest.
                Additionally, when you cast animate dead you can forgo animating three undead to instead animate the
                remains of one Large humanoid or giant. The resulting undead uses the statistics of a Minotaur Zombie if
                you target bones, or an Ogre Zombie if you target a corpse. You treat this creature as three corpses for
                the purpose of reasserting control over it.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Alter Overflow: Split Beam -->
    <element name="Alter Overflow: Split Beam" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ALTER_OVERFLOW_SPLIT_BEAM">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>On your turn, you can use your bonus action and forgo the use of your Eldritch Overflow feature to
                concentrate magical energy until the end of the turn. The next time you cast a cantrip in the duration,
                you can cast the same cantrip one more time as part of the same action.
            </p>
            <p>You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                On your turn, you can use your bonus action and forgo the use of your Eldritch Overflow feature to
                concentrate magical energy until the end of the turn. The next time you cast a cantrip in the duration,
                you can cast the same cantrip one more time as part of the same action.
                You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Alter Overflow: Perfected Arcana -->
    <element name="Alter Overflow: Perfected Arcana" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ALTER_OVERFLOW_PERFECTED_ARCANA">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>When you miss a creature with an attack that qualifies for your Eldritch Overflow feature, or a creature
                succeeds on saving throw against one of your warlock cantrips, you can force the attack to hit or the
                creature to fail the saving throw.
            </p>
            <p>You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns. Once you use this invocation, you must
                finish a short or long rest before you can do it again.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                When you miss a creature with an attack that qualifies for your Eldritch Overflow feature, or a creature
                succeeds on saving throw against one of your warlock cantrips, you can force the attack to hit or the
                creature to fail the saving throw.
                You can only use one Alter Overflow effect on each of your turns. Once you use this invocation, you must
                finish a short or long rest before you can do it again.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Grasp of the Fallen -->
    <element name="Grasp of the Fallen" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_GRASP_OF_THE_FALLEN">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>9th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:9]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can cast Maximilian's earthen grasp at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.
                When a creature dies while in the hand's grasp, you can summon a second hand for the spell's duration.
                When you use your action to direct the hand, you direct only one hand at a time. When you command the
                hand to crush, you can command both hands at once.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can cast Maximilian's earthen grasp at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.
                When a creature dies while in the hand's grasp, you can summon a second hand for the spell's duration.
                When you use your action to direct the hand, you direct only one hand at a time. When you command the
                hand to crush, you can command both hands at once.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Mastered Arcanum -->
    <element name="Mastered Arcanum" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MASTERED_ARCANUM">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>15th level</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:15]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can pick an additional spell for your Mystic Arcanum.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can pick an additional spell for your Mystic Arcanum.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Unearthly Alacrity -->
    <element name="Unearthly Alacrity" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_UNEARTHLY_ALACRITY">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Pact of the Blade feature</prerequisite>
        <requirements>ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_BLADE</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can take the Dash action as a bonus action. Additionally, your movement speed increases by 5 feet,
                you learn the zephyr strike spell, and can cast it without expending a warlock spell slot once per long
                rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can take the Dash action as a bonus action. Additionally, your movement speed increases by 5 feet,
                you learn the zephyr strike spell, and can cast it without expending a warlock spell slot once per long
                rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Moon-touched Armament -->
    <element name="Moon-touched Armament" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_MOON_TOUCHED_ARMAMENT">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>Moon Patron, Pact of the Blade</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[moonpatron,pactoftheblade]</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You can create a weapon of polished mithral capped with a shining moonstone using your Pact of the Blade
                feature. You can choose for this weapon to deal radiant or cold damage. While wielding this weapon, you
                have advantage on initiative checks.
            </p>
            <p>Whenever you hit a creature with this weapon, you can unleash a blast of moonlight. The target and every
                creature of your choice within 10 feet of it must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw against your
                Warlock Spell Save DC. A target takes damage equal to the weapon's damage + your warlock spellcasting
                ability modifier on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. You can do this a number
                of times equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier per short or long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You can create a weapon of polished mithral capped with a shining moonstone using your Pact of the Blade
                feature. You can choose for this weapon to deal radiant or cold damage. While wielding this weapon, you
                have advantage on initiative checks.
                Whenever you hit a creature with this weapon, you can unleash a blast of moonlight. The target and every
                creature of your choice within 10 feet of it must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw against your
                Warlock Spell Save DC. A target takes damage equal to the weapon's damage + your warlock spellcasting
                ability modifier on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. You can do this a number
                of times equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier per short or long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Scribe of Ancient Knowledge -->
    <element name="Scribe of Ancient Knowledge" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_SCRIBE_OF_ANCIENT_KNOWLEDGE">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>5th level, Pact of the Tome</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:5],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_TOME</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>Instead of knowing spells, you now prepare a number of spells equal to the Spells Known column of the
                warlock table plus your warlock spellcasting ability modifier from the warlock spell list. A spell you
                choose must be of a level no greater than what's shown in the Warlock table's Slot Level column for your
                level. You can change any number of your prepared spells whenever you finish a long rest.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                Instead of knowing spells, you now prepare a number of spells equal to the Spells Known column of the
                warlock table plus your warlock spellcasting ability modifier from the warlock spell list. A spell you
                choose must be of a level no greater than what's shown in the Warlock table's Slot Level column for your
                level. You can change any number of your prepared spells whenever you finish a long rest.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <!-- Bound By Blood -->
    <element name="Bound By Blood" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_BOUND_BY_BLOOD">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level, Pact of the Chain</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_CHAIN</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>Whenever your companion is reduced to 0 hit points, you can spend one hit die to reduce your familiar to
                1 hit point instead. Additionally, choose Strength, Dexterity, Constitution, Intelligence or Wisdom.
                Whenever your companion is subjected to an effect that would allow it to make a saving throw of the
                chosen ability score to take half damage, it instead takes no damage on a success and half damage on a
                failure.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                Whenever your companion is reduced to 0 hit points, you can spend one hit die to reduce your familiar to
                1 hit point instead. Additionally, choose Strength, Dexterity, Constitution, Intelligence or Wisdom.
                Whenever your companion is subjected to an effect that would allow it to make a saving throw of the
                chosen ability score to take half damage, it instead takes no damage on a success and half damage on a
                failure.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
    <!-- Arcane Inscription -->
    <element name="Arcane Inscription" type="Class Feature" source="Warlock Remastered"
             id="ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_ELDRITCH_INVOCATION_ARCANE_INSCRIPTION">
        <supports>Eldritch Invocation</supports>
        <prerequisite>7th level, Pact of the Tome</prerequisite>
        <requirements>[level:7],ID_HB_WR_CLASS_FEATURE_PACT_BOON_PACT_OF_TOME</requirements>
        <description>
            <p>You learn the secrets of transferring spells, granting your allies powers beyond belief. You visibly
                inscribe the flesh of the creature with a warlock spell of 1st level or higher that you know, expending
                a spell slot appropriate to cast the spell. While the spell is inscribed, you cannot cast the inscribed
                spell. During your turn, you can use your bonus action to force the creature to use its reaction to
                immediately cast the spell in a manner of your choosing, selecting targets or effects as you desire. If
                the creature can't cast the spell, your bonus action is wasted. The creature uses its Intelligence or
                Charisma score (whichever is higher) as its spellcasting ability for this spell. Once the creature
                successfully casts the spell, or after 1 week, the inscription vanishes. You can maintain a number of
                inscriptions equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum 1) at a time. Inscribing
                another beyond this limit causes an inscription of your choosing to vanish.
            </p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>
                You learn the secrets of transferring spells, granting your allies powers beyond belief. You visibly
                inscribe the flesh of the creature with a warlock spell of 1st level or higher that you know, expending
                a spell slot appropriate to cast the spell. While the spell is inscribed, you cannot cast the inscribed
                spell. During your turn, you can use your bonus action to force the creature to use its reaction to
                immediately cast the spell in a manner of your choosing, selecting targets or effects as you desire. If
                the creature can't cast the spell, your bonus action is wasted. The creature uses its Intelligence or
                Charisma score (whichever is higher) as its spellcasting ability for this spell. Once the creature
                successfully casts the spell, or after 1 week, the inscription vanishes. You can maintain a number of
                inscriptions equal to your warlock spellcasting ability modifier (minimum 1) at a time. Inscribing
                another beyond this limit causes an inscription of your choosing to vanish.
            </description>
        </sheet>
    </element>
</elements>